<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="overview">Programme Overview
The MSc(CompSc) programme is a comprehensive postgraduate study programme provides advanced and in-depth learning in Computer Science.  The programme is credit unit based, with courses of both applied and fundamental nature.

Students can choose focussed streams of study or a comprehensive and diversified study in Computer Science, i.e. the General Stream.

Focussed streams of study represent a cohesive collection of related courses that provides both fundamental and in-depth exposure to students in a given ICT domain.  Students can extend and deepen their knowledge in the specialization streams in Cyber Security, Multimedia Computing and Financial Computing.

Stream of Study
Cyber Security
The Cyber Security Stream is a multidisciplinary area of study and professional activity concerned with state-of-the-art technology in cyber security. The curriculum covers different aspects of cyber security from different perspectives, including technical, organisational, human-oriented and legal.
Multimedia Computing
The Multimedia Computing Stream focuses on multimedia computing, communications, analytics, visualisation and applications.
Multimedia Computing encompasses media coding and processing, streaming-media middleware, media representations, real-time protocols, media analysis, and human-interaction and visualisation techniques.
Students are encouraged to develop innovative ideas using the latest development in technology such as mobile devices and big-data analytics.
Financial Computing
The Financial Computing Stream is the study of data and algorithms used in finance and the mathematics of computer programs that realise financial models or systems.
Financial Computing emphasises practical numerical methods and focuses on techniques that are directly applicable to business and financial analysis.
The emphasis will be in the computing aspect of the financial industry.
General Stream
The General Stream covers a broad, comprehensive range of Computer Science subjects, including a wide range of courses from which students can choose from. It offers students the most flexibility to design their own study portfolio based on their career aspiration or requirements.
Pattern of Study
Students are required to complete 72 credits of courses selected from the syllabus which must include capstone experience.

Enrolment Mode
Students can study in one of the following enrolment modes:

(a)Courses (60 credits)^ + Project (12 credits)

     i.e. 10 Courses + Project

OR

(b)Courses (48 credits)^ + Dissertation (24 credits)

     i.e. 8 Courses + Dissertation

^ Each course normally carries 6 credits

Selection of Courses
Students shall select courses in accordance with the regulations of the degree. To qualify as a graduate of Cyber Security, Financial Computing, or Multimedia Computing Stream, students must pass at least 4 stream specific courses (at least 24 credits in total) in the corresponding subject group, and undertake a dissertation or a project in the area of the corresponding stream. For General Stream, students can choose any discipline courses from any subject group, and undertake a dissertation or a project in any area in computer science

Students may select no more than 2 courses (at most 12 credits in total) offered by the MSc(ECom＆IComp) and MSc(Eng) curricula in the Faculty of Engineering as electives.



Enrolment Mode
(10 courses + Project)
Enrolment Mode
(8 courses + Dissertation)


Cyber Security / Financial Computing / Multimedia Computing Stream

General Stream

Cyber Security / Financial Computing / Multimedia Computing Stream

General Stream

Credits of courses

60

(include at least 24 credits in Stream Specific Courses in the candidate’s corresponding stream of study)

60

(i.e. normally 10 courses)

48

(include at least 24 credits in Stream Specific Courses in the candidate’s corresponding stream of study)

48

(i.e. normally 8 courses)

Capstone experience

12-credit Project (associated with the corresponding stream)

12-credit Project

24-credit Dissertation (associated with the corresponding stream)

24-credit Dissertation

Total:

72

72

72

72

Capstone Experience – Dissertations and Projects
The capstone experience will definitely be beneficial for students to put together what they have learnt in the programme and demonstrate a deeper understanding of the knowledge they have acquired. Students are required to complete a dissertation (24 credits) or a project (12 credits), and attend some supplementary workshops. The dissertation / project would represent students’ consolidated capstone experience in their study.</string>
</resources>